so I rented a vacant retail space in Las
VES California that would serve as the
location for the first Dumb Starbucks
it's reminds me of the metal in my house
you have metal in your house oh
construction began immediately and it
would take at least a week to build the
shop so in the meantime I posted an ad
on Craigslist seeking Baristas with
Starbucks experience and after receiving
some responses I met with the applicants
to see if they'd be a good fit when
you're interacting with customers you
know it's important to have a good sense
of humor mhm do you have a good sense of
humor yeah I think so so let's see some
of that hi hey how's it going how's your
day great yeah it's going well it's
going well how's the weather enjoying
the weather yeah yeah that's cool I'm
not it's just too warm and I'm getting
over a sickness too so it's even more
warm than I'd like it to be that was
funny thanks Jeremiah was perfect for
the job I also hired Amber since we seem
to have a lot in common what would you
say is your greatest weakness my
greatest weakness is that I'm too nice
that's so funny that's it that happens
to be my greatest weakness too really
yeah and with the store set to open in
less than 24 hours my crew and I put the
final touches on making my parody
Starbucks look as authentic as
possible
[Music]